<?xml version="1.0"?>
<add><doc> 
	 
		http://library.marist.edu/archives/LTP/LTP.xml1.1 
		 
			 
				Lowell Thomas Papers 
			
			
				Marist College
				April 2010
				
					3399 North Road
					Poughkeepsie, NY 12601
				
				
			
		
		 
		 
			NPkMC
			Marist College Archives &amp; Special Collections
		
		
		
	
	 
		 
			 
				Marist College
				
					3399 North Road
					Poughkeepsie, NY 12601
				
			
			
					Thomas
					Lowell
					1892-1981
				
			Lowell Thomas Papers 
			MA-1 
			
			
			
			
		
		 
			Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
		
		 
			Individuals requesting reproductions expressly assume the responsibility for compliance with all pertinent provisions of the Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. ss101 et seq. Patrons further agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Marist College Archives &amp; http://www.loc.gov/copyright/title17/.
		
		 
			The Lowell Thomas Papers encompasses a wide range of materials documenting the life, family, and professional career of Lowell Thomas.
		
		 
			Lowell Jackson Thomas was born in Woodington, Ohio on 6 April 1892 to two school teachers, Harry G. Thomas and Harriet Wagner Thomas.  
		
		
				Thomas
				Lowell
				1892-1981
			
				Journalism
				United States
			
		
			
				
					MA-1-01
					Textual materials
					
				
				
					
						Correspondence, writings, and other material
						MA-1-01-01
						
						
					
					
						These files contain correspondence between Thomas family members; published and manuscript writings by Lowell Thomas, including autobiographical content, articles, speeches, and travelogues; and topically-arranged collections of journal articles, newspaper clippings, and ephemera.
					
				
				
					
						American Expeditionary Forces (A.E.F.)
						MA-1-01-02
						
						
						
					
				
				
					
						General Edmund Allenby
						MA-1-01-03
						
						
						
					
				
			
			
				
					MA-1-02
					Graphic materials
					
					
				
				
					Comprises photographs, lantern slides, and glass plate negatives accumulated by Frank R. Roberson and Lowell Thomas arranged by topic and geographic coverage.  
				
				
						Dalai Lama XIV
						1935-
					
			
		
	
</doc></add>
